{
	"description": "Kanji for 日本漢字能力検定 準1級",
	"deck": [
	{ "question": "一揖", "answers": [ "いちゆう" ] },
	{ "question": "一瞥", "answers": [ "いちべつ" ], "comment": "(a) glance; (a) look" },
	{ "question": "上巳", "answers": [ "じょうし" ], "comment": "March 3rd of the lunar calendar (one of the five annual festivals); dolls festival; peach festival" },
	{ "question": "不壊", "answers": [ "ふえ" ], "comment": "indestructibility" },
	{ "question": "井蛙", "answers": [ "せいあ" ], "comment": "frog in a well; someone with a narrow perspective" },
	{ "question": "些か", "answers": [ "いささか" ], "comment": "a little; a bit; somewhat; slightly; rather" },
	{ "question": "些事", "answers": [ "さじ" ], "comment": "something small or petty; trifle" },
	{ "question": "些少", "answers": [ "さしょう" ], "comment": "trifling; little; few; slight" },
	{ "question": "亡骸", "answers": [ "なきがら" ], "comment": "remains; corpse; (dead) body" },
	{ "question": "交誼", "answers": [ "こうぎ" ], "comment": "friendship; amity" },
	{ "question": "亥中", "answers": [ "いなか" ] },
	{ "question": "佃煮", "answers": [ "つくだに" ], "comment": "preserved food boiled in soy" },
	{ "question": "侮蔑", "answers": [ "ぶべつ" ], "comment": "scorn; disdain; contempt; slight" },
	{ "question": "俄か", "answers": [ "にわか" ], "comment": "sudden; abrupt; unexpected; improvised; hasty; offhand\nimpromptu skit" },
	{ "question": "俄然", "answers": [ "がぜん" ], "comment": "suddenly; all of a sudden; abruptly" },
	{ "question": "俗諺", "answers": [ "ぞくげん" ], "comment": "proverb; popular saying" },
	{ "question": "倦厭", "answers": [ "けんえん" ], "comment": "weariness" },
	{ "question": "僻事", "answers": [ "ひがごと" ], "comment": "immoral act; mistake" },
	{ "question": "僻見", "answers": [ "へきけん" ], "comment": "prejudice" },
	{ "question": "僻遠", "answers": [ "へきえん" ], "comment": "remote; outlying" },
	{ "question": "優渥", "answers": [ "ゆうあく" ], "comment": "gracious" },
	{ "question": "儲君", "answers": [ "ちょくん" ] },
	{ "question": "允可", "answers": [ "いんか" ], "comment": "permission; assent; compliance" },
	{ "question": "允許", "answers": [ "いんきょ" ], "comment": "permission; licence; license" },
	{ "question": "兇刃", "answers": [ "きょうじん" ], "comment": "assassin's dagger" },
	{ "question": "先鋒", "answers": [ "せんぽう" ], "comment": "advance guard; vanguard\nathlete who competes in the first match of a team competition (kendo, judo, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "光耀", "answers": [ "こうよう" ], "comment": "shining; glittering" },
	{ "question": "兜巾", "answers": [ "ときん" ], "comment": "black headgear worn by yamabushi" },
	{ "question": "八重葎", "answers": [ "やえむぐら" ], "comment": "thick patch of mixed weeds\nfalse cleavers (species of bedstraw, Galium spurium var. echinospermon)" },
	{ "question": "冒涜", "answers": [ "ぼうとく" ], "comment": "blasphemy; curse; profanity; sacrilege; desecration" },
	{ "question": "冥利", "answers": [ "みょうり" ], "comment": "providence; luck; favor; favour; advantage" },
	{ "question": "冴える", "answers": [ "さえる" ], "comment": "to be clear (of a sight, sound, colour, etc.); to be bright; to be vivid; to be crisp\nto be clear-headed; to be alert; to be on the ball; to be wide awake\nto look upbeat; to be perky; to be cheerful\nto master (a skill); to excel at; to cleanly execute\nto be satisfying\nto become frigid; to become intensely cold" },
	{ "question": "凄絶", "answers": [ "せいぜつ" ], "comment": "extremely gruesome; lurid; violent; bloody; fierce" },
	{ "question": "凋落", "answers": [ "ちょうらく" ], "comment": "decline; fall; decay; withering" },
	{ "question": "凌雲", "answers": [ "りょううん" ], "comment": "skyscraping; very high; above the clouds; above this mortal world" },
	{ "question": "凌駕", "answers": [ "りょうが" ], "comment": "excelling; surpassing; outdoing" },
	{ "question": "凛凛しい", "answers": [ "りりしい" ], "comment": "gallant; brave; imposing; awe-inspiring; severe; biting; chivalrous; manly; dignified" },
	{ "question": "凱旋", "answers": [ "がいせん" ], "comment": "triumphal return" },
	{ "question": "出鱈目", "answers": [ "でたらめ" ], "comment": "irresponsible utterance; nonsense; bullshit; codswallop\nrandom; haphazard; unsystematic" },
	{ "question": "初鰹", "answers": [ "はつがつお" ], "comment": "the first bonito of the season" },
	{ "question": "劫掠", "answers": [ "ごうりゃく" ], "comment": "pillage; plunder" },
	{ "question": "劫末", "answers": [ "ごうまつ" ] },
	{ "question": "匡正", "answers": [ "きょうせい" ], "comment": "correction (of error, mistake, etc.); reform; training" },
	{ "question": "半纏", "answers": [ "はんてん" ], "comment": "traditional short winter coat resembling a haori without gussets\nlivery coat" },
	{ "question": "卜占", "answers": [ "ぼくせん" ], "comment": "augury; fortune-telling; divination" },
	{ "question": "卯月", "answers": [ "うづき" ], "comment": "fourth month of the lunar calendar" },
	{ "question": "危殆", "answers": [ "きたい" ], "comment": "danger; jeopardy; distress" },
	{ "question": "卿相", "answers": [ "けいしょう" ], "comment": "court nobles and state ministers" },
	{ "question": "厨子", "answers": [ "ずし" ], "comment": "miniature shrine with double doors (used to store important Buddhist items such as sutras, etc.)\ncabinet with double doors (used by the nobility to store books, etc.)\n(in Okinawa) carved and decorated stone container for storing the bones of one's ancestors" },
	{ "question": "厩肥", "answers": [ "きゅうひ" ], "comment": "manure; compost" },
	{ "question": "厩舎", "answers": [ "きゅうしゃ" ], "comment": "barn; stable" },
	{ "question": "厭悪", "answers": [ "えんお" ], "comment": "dislike; detestation" },
	{ "question": "友誼", "answers": [ "ゆうぎ" ], "comment": "friendship; friendly relations; fellowship" },
	{ "question": "吃る", "answers": [ "どもる" ], "comment": "to stammer; to stutter" },
	{ "question": "吻合", "answers": [ "ふんごう" ], "comment": "coincidence; conformity\nanastomosis; inosculation" },
	{ "question": "呆気", "answers": [ "あっけ" ], "comment": "taken aback; dumbfounded" },
	{ "question": "呆然", "answers": [ "ぼうぜん" ], "comment": "dumbfounded; overcome with surprise; in blank amazement; in a daze" },
	{ "question": "呪術", "answers": [ "じゅじゅつ" ], "comment": "magic; sorcery; incantation" },
	{ "question": "咽喉", "answers": [ "いんこう" ], "comment": "throat" },
	{ "question": "唖然", "answers": [ "あぜん" ], "comment": "dumbfounded; in mute amazement" },
	{ "question": "喋喋", "answers": [ "ちょうちょう" ] },
	{ "question": "喧しい", "answers": [ "やかましい" ], "comment": "noisy; boisterous\nstrict; faultfinding; carping; fussy\nnoisy; boisterous" },
	{ "question": "喧伝", "answers": [ "けんでん" ], "comment": "spreading around (news, etc.); talking about widely" },
	{ "question": "喧嘩", "answers": [ "けんか" ], "comment": "quarrel; brawl; fight; squabble; scuffle; argument" },
	{ "question": "嘗試", "answers": [ "しょうし" ] },
	{ "question": "嚢中", "answers": [ "のうちゅう" ], "comment": "in a bag or one's purse" },
	{ "question": "土嚢", "answers": [ "どのう" ], "comment": "sandbag" },
	{ "question": "坤軸", "answers": [ "こんじく" ] },
	{ "question": "城砦", "answers": [ "じょうさい" ], "comment": "fortress; stronghold; citadel" },
	{ "question": "堅牢", "answers": [ "けんろう" ], "comment": "solid; strong; sturdy; durable; stout" },
	{ "question": "堆積", "answers": [ "たいせき" ], "comment": "accumulation; pile; heap\nsedimentation" },
	{ "question": "堰堤", "answers": [ "えんてい" ], "comment": "dam; weir" },
	{ "question": "堰塞", "answers": [ "えんそく" ], "comment": "damming (e.g. a pond)" },
	{ "question": "填足", "answers": [ "てんそく" ] },
	{ "question": "塵芥", "answers": [ "じんかい", "ちりあくた", "ごみあくた" ], "comment": "rubbish; trash; garbage; refuse\nworthless thing" },
	{ "question": "壺中", "answers": [ "こちゅう" ], "comment": "inside a jar\ncoward; timid person" },
	{ "question": "外甥", "answers": [ "がいせい" ] },
	{ "question": "夙夜", "answers": [ "しゅくや" ], "comment": "from morning till night; day and night; always" },
	{ "question": "夜叉", "answers": [ "やしゃ" ], "comment": "yaksha (Buddhist guardian deities sometimes depicted as demonic warriors)" },
	{ "question": "天秤", "answers": [ "てんびん" ], "comment": "(balance) scales\nshoulder carrying pole\nsteelyard" },
	{ "question": "天蓋", "answers": [ "てんがい" ], "comment": "canopy; dome\npriestly minstrel's reed hood; reed hood worn by Komuso priests" },
	{ "question": "姦しい", "answers": [ "かしましい" ], "comment": "noisy; boisterous" },
	{ "question": "嫉妬", "answers": [ "しっと" ], "comment": "jealousy; envy" },
	{ "question": "嬰児", "answers": [ "えいじ" ], "comment": "infant; baby" },
	{ "question": "孜孜", "answers": [ "しし" ], "comment": "assiduously; diligently" },
	{ "question": "室鯵", "answers": [ "むろあじ" ], "comment": "brownstriped mackerel scad (Decapterus muroadsi)\nmackerel scad (any fish of genus Decapterus)" },
	{ "question": "宥和", "answers": [ "ゆうわ" ], "comment": "appeasement" },
	{ "question": "宥恕", "answers": [ "ゆうじょ" ], "comment": "forgiveness; generosity" },
	{ "question": "家禽", "answers": [ "かきん" ], "comment": "poultry; fowls" },
	{ "question": "尖端", "answers": [ "せんたん" ], "comment": "pointed end; tip; fine point; spearhead; cusp; vanguard; advanced; leading edge; apex (of a curve)" },
	{ "question": "尤物", "answers": [ "ゆうぶつ" ], "comment": "something superior; beautiful woman" },
	{ "question": "屑屑", "answers": [ "せつせつ" ] },
	{ "question": "屡次", "answers": [ "るじ" ] },
	{ "question": "峨峨", "answers": [ "がが" ], "comment": "rugged (e.g. mountains)" },
	{ "question": "巌頭", "answers": [ "がんとう" ], "comment": "top of a massive rock" },
	{ "question": "巽位", "answers": [ "そんい" ] },
	{ "question": "庇護", "answers": [ "ひご" ], "comment": "patronage; protection" },
	{ "question": "廓清", "answers": [ "かくせい" ], "comment": "purification; cleaning up; purging" },
	{ "question": "廟議", "answers": [ "びょうぎ" ] },
	{ "question": "廻船", "answers": [ "かいせん" ], "comment": "lighter; (small) cargo vessel" },
	{ "question": "弄舌", "answers": [ "ろうぜつ" ] },
	{ "question": "弘誓", "answers": [ "ぐぜい" ], "comment": "Buddha's great vows" },
	{ "question": "弥漫", "answers": [ "びまん" ], "comment": "pervasion" },
	{ "question": "強か", "answers": [ "したたか" ], "comment": "tough; stubborn; determined; hard\nseverely; heavily; hard; a great deal; much" },
	{ "question": "強靱", "answers": [ "きょうじん" ], "comment": "tough; strong; stiff; tenacious" },
	{ "question": "形骸", "answers": [ "けいがい" ], "comment": "ruin; wreck; mere skeleton; framework" },
	{ "question": "律呂", "answers": [ "りつりょ" ], "comment": "standard tones; Chinese system of musical sounds" },
	{ "question": "後胤", "answers": [ "こういん" ], "comment": "descendant; scion" },
	{ "question": "徽章", "answers": [ "きしょう" ], "comment": "medal; badge; insignia" },
	{ "question": "忌引", "answers": [ "きびき" ], "comment": "absence from work (school) due to mourning" },
	{ "question": "忌日", "answers": [ "きじつ" ], "comment": "anniversary of a person's death (on which Buddhist commemorative rites, etc. are performed)\n49th day after a person's death, on which Buddhist rituals are performed\nunlucky day (according to astrology); (previously a) death anniversary; purification and fast day" },
	{ "question": "快哉", "answers": [ "かいさい" ], "comment": "joy; exultation" },
	{ "question": "忽然", "answers": [ "こつぜん" ], "comment": "sudden; unexpected" },
	{ "question": "急く", "answers": [ "せく" ], "comment": "to hurry; to rush" },
	{ "question": "怯える", "answers": [ "おびえる" ], "comment": "to become frightened; to be frightened (of); to be scared (of)" },
	{ "question": "怯む", "answers": [ "ひるむ" ], "comment": "to falter; to flinch (from); to recoil (from); to quail (at)" },
	{ "question": "怯夫", "answers": [ "きょうふ" ] },
	{ "question": "恰も", "answers": [ "あたかも" ], "comment": "as if; as it were; as though\nright then; just then; at that moment" },
	{ "question": "恰幅", "answers": [ "かっぷく" ], "comment": "physique; bodily build" },
	{ "question": "悉く", "answers": [ "ことごとく" ], "comment": "altogether; entirely" },
	{ "question": "悉皆", "answers": [ "しっかい" ], "comment": "all" },
	{ "question": "悶絶", "answers": [ "もんぜつ" ], "comment": "fainting in agony" },
	{ "question": "惣菜", "answers": [ "そうざい" ], "comment": "side dish; daily (household) dish" },
	{ "question": "慧眼", "answers": [ "けいがん" ], "comment": "discerning (quick) eye; keen insight\nthe wisdom eye" },
	{ "question": "戎馬", "answers": [ "じゅうば" ], "comment": "warhorse" },
	{ "question": "所謂", "answers": [ "いわゆる" ], "comment": "what is called; as it is called; the so-called; so to speak" },
	{ "question": "手筈", "answers": [ "てはず" ], "comment": "arrangement; plan; programme; program" },
	{ "question": "托鉢", "answers": [ "たくはつ" ], "comment": "monk's \"begging\"; religious mendicancy; asking for alms\ngoing with one's bowl to the meditation hall at mealtime (in a Zen temple)" },
	{ "question": "抜擢", "answers": [ "ばってき" ], "comment": "selection (esp. from many people for an important job position); exceptional promotion" },
	{ "question": "拳固", "answers": [ "げんこ" ], "comment": "fist" },
	{ "question": "按摩", "answers": [ "あんま" ], "comment": "massage, esp. the Anma Japanese type of massage\nmasseur; masseuse; massager\nblind person (as many were traditionally massagers)" },
	{ "question": "挙って", "answers": [ "こぞって" ], "comment": "all; all together; unanimously" },
	{ "question": "挽歌", "answers": [ "ばんか" ], "comment": "elegy; funeral song" },
	{ "question": "捺印", "answers": [ "なついん" ], "comment": "affixing a seal" },
	{ "question": "掠める", "answers": [ "かすめる" ], "comment": "to steal; to rob; to snatch; to pocket; to plunder\nto deceive; to trick; to cheat\nto graze (in passing); to skim; to brush against; to touch lightly\nto appear and quickly disappear (a thought, a smile, etc.); to flit (through one's mind, across one's face)\nto do (something) while no one is looking\nto hint at; to suggest; to insinuate" },
	{ "question": "推挽", "answers": [ "すいばん" ] },
	{ "question": "掩蔽", "answers": [ "えんぺい" ], "comment": "cover; concealment; masking; screening\noccultation" },
	{ "question": "掬う", "answers": [ "すくう" ], "comment": "to scoop; to ladle out" },
	{ "question": "揖譲", "answers": [ "ゆうじょう" ], "comment": "bowing respectfully with one's hands clasped in front of one's chest\nabdication of an emperor to a successor (China)" },
	{ "question": "播植", "answers": [ "はしょく" ] },
	{ "question": "撹拌", "answers": [ "かくはん", "こうはん" ], "comment": "agitation; stirring; whipping; beating" },
	{ "question": "敏捷", "answers": [ "びんしょう" ], "comment": "nimble; prompt; agile; quick; shrewd; smart" },
	{ "question": "斡旋", "answers": [ "あっせん" ], "comment": "kind offices; services; through the good offices of; influence\nintercession; mediation" },
	{ "question": "旺盛", "answers": [ "おうせい" ], "comment": "full of vim and vigor" },
	{ "question": "晒す", "answers": [ "さらす" ], "comment": "to expose (to the sun, public, danger, etc.)\nto bleach; to refine\nto rinse (vegetables); to soak\nto sentence someone to public humiliation" },
	{ "question": "晦渋", "answers": [ "かいじゅう" ], "comment": "ambiguous; obscure; equivocal" },
	{ "question": "暢達", "answers": [ "ちょうたつ" ], "comment": "fluency; facileness" },
	{ "question": "暴戻", "answers": [ "ぼうれい" ], "comment": "tyranny; atrocity" },
	{ "question": "曳航", "answers": [ "えいこう" ], "comment": "towing (a ship)" },
	{ "question": "有卦", "answers": [ "うけ" ], "comment": "streak of good luck" },
	{ "question": "木鐸", "answers": [ "ぼくたく" ], "comment": "bell with wooden clapper\nleader; guide (of the public)" },
	{ "question": "杏林", "answers": [ "きょうりん" ], "comment": "apricot grove" },
	{ "question": "枇杷", "answers": [ "びわ" ], "comment": "loquat (Eriobotrya japonica); Japanese medlar" },
	{ "question": "枕頭", "answers": [ "ちんとう" ], "comment": "bedside" },
	{ "question": "枯凋", "answers": [ "こちょう" ] },
	{ "question": "柑橘", "answers": [ "かんきつ" ], "comment": "citrus; citrus fruit" },
	{ "question": "柴扉", "answers": [ "さいひ" ] },
	{ "question": "栗毛", "answers": [ "くりげ" ], "comment": "chestnut (horse coat color)" },
	{ "question": "桔梗", "answers": [ "ききょう" ], "comment": "Chinese bellflower; Platycodon grandiflorum" },
	{ "question": "梓弓", "answers": [ "あずさゆみ" ], "comment": "catalpa bow; spirit bow; bow used to summon spirits, made of Japanese cherry birch, catalpa, or other wood" },
	{ "question": "椰子", "answers": [ "やし" ], "comment": "palm tree" },
	{ "question": "椿寿", "answers": [ "ちんじゅ" ], "comment": "longevity; long life" },
	{ "question": "横溢", "answers": [ "おういつ" ], "comment": "overflowing; inundation" },
	{ "question": "檜扇", "answers": [ "ひおうぎ" ], "comment": "formal folding fan made of hinoki cypress\nblackberry lily (Belamcanda Chinensis); leopard lily; leopard flower" },
	{ "question": "櫛比", "answers": [ "しっぴ" ], "comment": "lining up; packing tightly" },
	{ "question": "欠片", "answers": [ "かけら" ], "comment": "fragment; broken pieces; splinter" },
	{ "question": "欽慕", "answers": [ "きんぼ" ], "comment": "adoration; reverence; admiration" },
	{ "question": "歌唄", "answers": [ "かばい" ] },
	{ "question": "正閏", "answers": [ "せいじゅん" ], "comment": "normal and leap (years)\nlegitimate and illegitimate dynasties" },
	{ "question": "歪曲", "answers": [ "わいきょく" ], "comment": "distortion; falsification; perversion" },
	{ "question": "歯垢", "answers": [ "しこう" ], "comment": "(dental) plaque" },
	{ "question": "歯牙", "answers": [ "しが" ], "comment": "teeth (and tusks)" },
	{ "question": "残蝉", "answers": [ "ざんせん" ] },
	{ "question": "毅然", "answers": [ "きぜん" ], "comment": "fortitude; firmness; resolution" },
	{ "question": "毒蛾", "answers": [ "どくが" ], "comment": "poisonous moth" },
	{ "question": "汀渚", "answers": [ "ていしょ" ], "comment": "sand bar; waters edge" },
	{ "question": "汲水", "answers": [ "きゅうすい" ] },
	{ "question": "沃土", "answers": [ "よくど" ], "comment": "rich soil; fertile land" },
	{ "question": "沓石", "answers": [ "くついし" ] },
	{ "question": "沫雪", "answers": [ "あわゆき" ], "comment": "light snowfall" },
	{ "question": "洞察", "answers": [ "どうさつ" ], "comment": "discernment; insight" },
	{ "question": "流暢", "answers": [ "りゅうちょう" ], "comment": "fluent (language skill); flowing" },
	{ "question": "浮腫", "answers": [ "ふしゅ" ], "comment": "swelling; edema; oedema" },
	{ "question": "深淵", "answers": [ "しんえん" ], "comment": "abyss; ravine" },
	{ "question": "清穆", "answers": [ "せいぼく" ], "comment": "gentle and pure (used in letters to celebrate the health and happiness of the addressee)" },
	{ "question": "渠魁", "answers": [ "きょかい" ], "comment": "ringleader; chief" },
	{ "question": "湛える", "answers": [ "たたえる" ], "comment": "to fill (to the brim)\nto express (an emotion); to look (sad, glad); to wear (a smile)" },
	{ "question": "湛然", "answers": [ "たんぜん" ] },
	{ "question": "満腔", "answers": [ "まんこう" ], "comment": "heartfelt; sincere; wholehearted; in one's whole body" },
	{ "question": "溝渠", "answers": [ "こうきょ" ], "comment": "ditch; sewer; canal" },
	{ "question": "溢れる", "answers": [ "あふれる" ], "comment": "to fail (in getting a job); to miss out (at fishing, hunting, etc.)\nto be left out; to be crowded out\nto overflow; to brim over; to flood\nto spill; to fall out of; to overflow\nto peek through; to become visible (although normally not)\nto escape (of a smile, tear, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "溢水", "answers": [ "いっすい" ], "comment": "inundation; overflow" },
	{ "question": "溢美", "answers": [ "いつび" ] },
	{ "question": "漏洩", "answers": [ "ろうえい" ], "comment": "disclosure; leak (of information); divulging\nleakage (e.g. of gas or liquids); leak; escape (e.g. of gas); coming in (through) (e.g. of light)" },
	{ "question": "潟湖", "answers": [ "せきこ" ], "comment": "lagoon" },
	{ "question": "濃艶", "answers": [ "のうえん" ], "comment": "charming; bewitching; enchanting" },
	{ "question": "濤声", "answers": [ "とうせい" ], "comment": "sound of waves" },
	{ "question": "灌漑", "answers": [ "かんがい" ], "comment": "irrigation" },
	{ "question": "灸", "answers": [ "きゅう" ], "comment": "moxibustion" },
	{ "question": "灸師", "answers": [ "きゅうし" ] },
	{ "question": "灼熱", "answers": [ "しゃくねつ" ], "comment": "red hot; white hot; scorching heat; incandescence" },
	{ "question": "烏", "answers": [ "からす" ], "comment": "crow (Corvus spp.); raven" },
	{ "question": "烏合", "answers": [ "うごう" ], "comment": "disorderly gathering" },
	{ "question": "烏有", "answers": [ "うゆう" ], "comment": "nonexistence" },
	{ "question": "焚刑", "answers": [ "ふんけい" ], "comment": "burning at the stake" },
	{ "question": "熊掌", "answers": [ "ゆうしょう" ], "comment": "bear's palm (meat treasured in Ancient China)" },
	{ "question": "熔解", "answers": [ "ようかい" ], "comment": "melting; liquefying; fusion" },
	{ "question": "燕尾服", "answers": [ "えんびふく" ], "comment": "tailcoat" },
	{ "question": "燦燦", "answers": [ "さんさん" ], "comment": "brilliant; bright" },
	{ "question": "爾後", "answers": [ "じご" ], "comment": "thereafter" },
	{ "question": "爾来", "answers": [ "じらい" ], "comment": "since then; after that" },
	{ "question": "牙城", "answers": [ "がじょう" ], "comment": "stronghold (esp. of an enemy or opponent); inner citadel; bastion" },
	{ "question": "牝牡", "answers": [ "ひんぼ" ] },
	{ "question": "牡牛", "answers": [ "おうし" ], "comment": "bull; ox; steer" },
	{ "question": "牡蠣", "answers": [ "かき" ], "comment": "oyster; oyster shell" },
	{ "question": "犀利", "answers": [ "さいり" ], "comment": "sharp; keen" },
	{ "question": "狐狸", "answers": [ "こり" ], "comment": "foxes and tanuki\nsly fellow; deceiver" },
	{ "question": "狛犬", "answers": [ "こまいぬ" ], "comment": "(stone) guardian lion-dogs at Shinto shrine" },
	{ "question": "独活", "answers": [ "うど" ], "comment": "udo (plant related to ginseng, used in medicine and cooking) (Aralia cordata)" },
	{ "question": "狭窄", "answers": [ "きょうさく" ], "comment": "stricture; stenosis; contraction" },
	{ "question": "玉葱", "answers": [ "たまねぎ" ], "comment": "onion (Allium cepa)" },
	{ "question": "甥姪", "answers": [ "せいてつ" ], "comment": "nephews and nieces" },
	{ "question": "田螺", "answers": [ "たにし" ], "comment": "pond snail (Viviparidae spp.)" },
	{ "question": "画餅", "answers": [ "がべい", "がへい" ], "comment": "something useless; picture of rice cakes" },
	{ "question": "畏怖", "answers": [ "いふ" ], "comment": "awe; fear; fright" },
	{ "question": "畢生", "answers": [ "ひっせい" ], "comment": "lifetime" },
	{ "question": "畦道", "answers": [ "あぜみち" ], "comment": "(raised) footpath between rice fields; ridge between rice fields" },
	{ "question": "痩躯", "answers": [ "そうく" ], "comment": "lean figure; slim figure" },
	{ "question": "白蟻", "answers": [ "しろあり" ], "comment": "termite; white ant" },
	{ "question": "目蓋", "answers": [ "まぶた" ], "comment": "eyelid; eyelids" },
	{ "question": "眉間", "answers": [ "みけん" ], "comment": "brow; glabella; middle forehead; area between the eyebrows" },
	{ "question": "真贋", "answers": [ "しんがん" ], "comment": "genuineness or spuriousness; authenticity; the genuine and the spurious" },
	{ "question": "真鰯", "answers": [ "まいわし" ], "comment": "Japanese pilchard; Japanese sardine (Sardinops melanostictus)" },
	{ "question": "矢鱈", "answers": [ "やたら" ], "comment": "indiscriminately; blindly; at random; recklessly; thoughtlessly; excessively; profusely\nindiscriminate; random; excessive" },
	{ "question": "知悉", "answers": [ "ちしつ" ], "comment": "complete knowledge" },
	{ "question": "矩形", "answers": [ "くけい" ], "comment": "rectangle" },
	{ "question": "石鹸", "answers": [ "せっけん" ], "comment": "soap" },
	{ "question": "砧声", "answers": [ "ちんせい" ] },
	{ "question": "碩学", "answers": [ "せきがく" ], "comment": "great scholar; profound scholar" },
	{ "question": "碩徳", "answers": [ "せきとく" ] },
	{ "question": "祁寒", "answers": [ "きかん" ] },
	{ "question": "神輿", "answers": [ "しんよ" ], "comment": "portable shrine (carried in festivals)\npalanquin\nbuttocks; lower back; waist; hips" },
	{ "question": "禽獣", "answers": [ "きんじゅう" ], "comment": "birds and animals" },
	{ "question": "私怨", "answers": [ "しえん" ], "comment": "personal grudge or enmity" },
	{ "question": "稀", "answers": [ "まれ" ], "comment": "rare; seldom\ndilute\nrare" },
	{ "question": "稀覯書", "answers": [ "きこうしょ" ] },
	{ "question": "稜線", "answers": [ "りょうせん" ], "comment": "ridgeline; lines of a mountain ridge" },
	{ "question": "穎才", "answers": [ "えいさい" ], "comment": "genius; brilliance; unusual talent\ngifted person; person of unusual talent" },
	{ "question": "穎異", "answers": [ "えいい" ] },
	{ "question": "空隙", "answers": [ "くうげき" ], "comment": "vacant space; aperture; gap; opening" },
	{ "question": "穿つ", "answers": [ "うがつ" ], "comment": "to drill; to bore; to pierce; to pass through\nto hit the mark; to get to the heart of (the matter); to be true to (nature)\nto put on; to wear" },
	{ "question": "窺う", "answers": [ "うかがう" ], "comment": "to peep (through); to peek; to examine (esp. covertly)\nto await (one's chance)\nto guess; to infer; to gather; to surmise" },
	{ "question": "立葵", "answers": [ "たちあおい" ], "comment": "hollyhock (Alcea rosea)" },
	{ "question": "筆鋒", "answers": [ "ひっぽう" ], "comment": "power of the pen" },
	{ "question": "箪笥", "answers": [ "たんす" ], "comment": "chest of drawers; bureau; cabinet; tansu; dresser" },
	{ "question": "簸却", "answers": [ "はきゃく" ] },
	{ "question": "粗忽", "answers": [ "そこつ" ], "comment": "careless; thoughtless; rash; rude; at fault" },
	{ "question": "糸鋸", "answers": [ "いとのこ" ], "comment": "coping saw; fretsaw; jig saw; jigsaw" },
	{ "question": "約やか", "answers": [ "つづまやか" ], "comment": "concise; brief\nhumble; frugal\nmodest; discrete" },
	{ "question": "紛擾", "answers": [ "ふんじょう" ], "comment": "disturbance; trouble; dispute" },
	{ "question": "素馨", "answers": [ "そけい" ], "comment": "Spanish jasmine (Jasminum grandiflorum)" },
	{ "question": "紫蘇", "answers": [ "しそ" ], "comment": "shiso (Perilla frutescens var. crispa); perilla; beefsteak plant" },
	{ "question": "縞柄", "answers": [ "しまがら" ], "comment": "striped pattern" },
	{ "question": "縞馬", "answers": [ "しまうま" ], "comment": "zebra" },
	{ "question": "縞鰺", "answers": [ "しまあじ" ], "comment": "striped jack (Pseudocaranx dentex); white trevally" },
	{ "question": "罫線", "answers": [ "けいせん" ], "comment": "ruled line; rule\nchart\ncrease; score" },
	{ "question": "翠微", "answers": [ "すいび" ], "comment": "approx. 80% of the way up a mountainside\nview of a light green mountain; mountain that appears green from afar" },
	{ "question": "翫弄", "answers": [ "がんろう" ], "comment": "making sport of; making a plaything of; toying with; trifling with; ridicule; mockery" },
	{ "question": "翰墨", "answers": [ "かんぼく" ], "comment": "brush and ink; writing; drawing" },
	{ "question": "老爺", "answers": [ "ろうや" ], "comment": "one's father; old man; one's boss" },
	{ "question": "耽る", "answers": [ "ふける" ], "comment": "to indulge in; to give oneself up to; to be obsessed by\nto be engrossed in; to be lost in; to be absorbed in" },
	{ "question": "耽読", "answers": [ "たんどく" ], "comment": "absorption in reading" },
	{ "question": "聯亙", "answers": [ "れんこう" ], "comment": "extending in a row" },
	{ "question": "聾唖", "answers": [ "ろうあ" ], "comment": "deafness\ndeaf-mute" },
	{ "question": "肋木", "answers": [ "ろくぼく" ], "comment": "wall bars" },
	{ "question": "背馳", "answers": [ "はいち" ], "comment": "inconsistency; contradiction; disobedience" },
	{ "question": "脆弱", "answers": [ "ぜいじゃく" ], "comment": "weak; frail; fragile" },
	{ "question": "脇息", "answers": [ "きょうそく" ], "comment": "armrest" },
	{ "question": "膝下", "answers": [ "しっか", "ひざもと" ], "comment": "near one's knee\nunder the protection of (e.g. one's parents); under the care of\nterritory of a powerful person\naddress used after the names of one's parents, grandparents, etc. in a letter\nbelow the knee" },
	{ "question": "艶冶", "answers": [ "えんや" ] },
	{ "question": "艶姿", "answers": [ "あですがた" ], "comment": "charming figure; alluring figure" },
	{ "question": "花圃", "answers": [ "かほ" ], "comment": "flower garden" },
	{ "question": "花蕊", "answers": [ "かずい" ], "comment": "center of a flower (centre); pistils and stamens" },
	{ "question": "芳醇", "answers": [ "ほうじゅん" ], "comment": "mellow (flavor or fragrance, esp. alcohol); rich; full-bodied; superior" },
	{ "question": "苧麻", "answers": [ "ちょま" ], "comment": "ramie (Boehmeria nivea var. nipononivea)" },
	{ "question": "茄子", "answers": [ "なす" ], "comment": "eggplant (Solanum melongena); aubergine" },
	{ "question": "茅屋", "answers": [ "ぼうおく" ], "comment": "thatched cottage; hovel; my humble cottage" },
	{ "question": "茅茨", "answers": [ "ぼうし" ] },
	{ "question": "茜色", "answers": [ "あかねいろ" ], "comment": "madder red" },
	{ "question": "荏苒", "answers": [ "じんぜん" ], "comment": "procrastination" },
	{ "question": "菖蒲", "answers": [ "しょうぶ" ], "comment": "sweet flag (Acorus calamus); calamus\nJapanese iris (Iris ensata var. ensata)\niris (flower)\nSiberian iris (Iris sanguinea)\nsweet flag (Acorus calamus); calamus" },
	{ "question": "萱堂", "answers": [ "けんどう" ], "comment": "mother" },
	{ "question": "落雁", "answers": [ "らくがん" ], "comment": "rakugan; dry confection of starch (e.g. rice, soy or barley flour) and sugar, mixed and pressed into a pattern\ngeese alighting" },
	{ "question": "葛藤", "answers": [ "かっとう" ], "comment": "conflict; complication; troubles; discord\nChinese moonseed (Sinomenium acutum)\ncomplex inter-relationship (as in the struggle between two types of vine over one piece of land)" },
	{ "question": "葡萄", "answers": [ "ぶどう" ], "comment": "grape; grapevine" },
	{ "question": "葦毛", "answers": [ "あしげ" ], "comment": "dapple-grey (gray) (horse coat colour)" },
	{ "question": "蒲鉾", "answers": [ "かまぼこ" ], "comment": "kamaboko; steamed seasoned fish paste, usu. in a semicylindrical shape on a strip of wood and sliced to go in soup, etc." },
	{ "question": "蓋世", "answers": [ "がいせい" ] },
	{ "question": "蓋棺", "answers": [ "がいかん" ] },
	{ "question": "蓬髪", "answers": [ "ほうはつ" ], "comment": "unkempt hair; disheveled hair; tousled hair" },
	{ "question": "蔓延", "answers": [ "まんえん" ], "comment": "spread (e.g. of a disease); rampancy; infestation; proliferation; being widespread" },
	{ "question": "蕩尽", "answers": [ "とうじん" ], "comment": "squandering; dissipation" },
	{ "question": "蕪辞", "answers": [ "ぶじ" ], "comment": "coarse speech or writing; humble reference to one's own words" },
	{ "question": "蘇生", "answers": [ "そせい" ], "comment": "rebirth; resuscitation; rehabilitation; reorganization; reorganisation; regeneration; resurrection; reviving" },
	{ "question": "虚ろ", "answers": [ "うつろ" ], "comment": "cavity; hollow; void\nhollow (voice); empty (heart); blank (eyes, face, etc.); vacant (stare)" },
	{ "question": "虞犯", "answers": [ "ぐはん" ], "comment": "likelihood of committing a crime; pre-delinquent" },
	{ "question": "虻", "answers": [ "あぶ" ], "comment": "horsefly; gadfly" },
	{ "question": "蜂起", "answers": [ "ほうき" ], "comment": "uprising; revolt" },
	{ "question": "螺旋", "answers": [ "らせん" ], "comment": "screw\nkey (of a clock, watch, etc.); spring (of a clock, watch, etc.)\nspiral; helix\nscrew" },
	{ "question": "衣桁", "answers": [ "いこう" ], "comment": "clothes rack" },
	{ "question": "補填", "answers": [ "ほてん" ], "comment": "compensating; making up for; supplementation" },
	{ "question": "襖", "answers": [ "ふすま" ], "comment": "fusuma; Japanese sliding screen\neveryday garment worn by men in ancient Japan" },
	{ "question": "誰何", "answers": [ "すいか" ], "comment": "challenging (an unknown person); asking a person's identity" },
	{ "question": "諌言", "answers": [ "かんげん" ], "comment": "admonition; remonstrance; expostulation" },
	{ "question": "謙遜", "answers": [ "けんそん" ], "comment": "modesty; humility; being humble" },
	{ "question": "謬見", "answers": [ "びゅうけん" ], "comment": "fallacy" },
	{ "question": "豊頬", "answers": [ "ほうきょう" ], "comment": "plump cheeks (used to describe a beautiful woman); attractive cheeks" },
	{ "question": "豪宕", "answers": [ "ごうとう" ], "comment": "breadth of soul; largeness of mind; magnanimity" },
	{ "question": "賭博", "answers": [ "とばく" ], "comment": "gambling" },
	{ "question": "贋作", "answers": [ "がんさく" ], "comment": "fake; sham; counterfeit" },
	{ "question": "赫怒", "answers": [ "かくど" ], "comment": "greatly enraged; furious" },
	{ "question": "赫然", "answers": [ "かくぜん" ], "comment": "violent and angry\nshining; glittering; sparkling" },
	{ "question": "起臥", "answers": [ "きが" ], "comment": "daily life; daily living; waking up and going to sleep" },
	{ "question": "足掻く", "answers": [ "あがく" ], "comment": "to paw (at) the ground\nto flounder; to struggle" },
	{ "question": "跨下", "answers": [ "こか" ] },
	{ "question": "輔弼", "answers": [ "ほひつ" ], "comment": "giving the Emperor advice on affairs of state; assistance; counsel" },
	{ "question": "迂回", "answers": [ "うかい" ], "comment": "detour\nto detour; to circumvent\nturning movement" },
	{ "question": "迂闊", "answers": [ "うかつ" ], "comment": "careless; stupid; thoughtless; heedless; unobservant; inadvertant; incautious" },
	{ "question": "退嬰", "answers": [ "たいえい" ] },
	{ "question": "這般", "answers": [ "しゃはん" ] },
	{ "question": "逢瀬", "answers": [ "おうせ" ], "comment": "rendezvous; tryst; (lover's) meeting; (secret) date" },
	{ "question": "遁辞", "answers": [ "とんじ" ], "comment": "excuse; evasive answer; subterfuge" },
	{ "question": "遮蔽", "answers": [ "しゃへい" ], "comment": "shielding; sheltering; screening; shading; masking" },
	{ "question": "都邑", "answers": [ "とゆう" ], "comment": "city; town; village" },
	{ "question": "酒肴", "answers": [ "しゅこう" ], "comment": "food and drink" },
	{ "question": "醍醐味", "answers": [ "だいごみ" ], "comment": "the real pleasure (of something); the real thrill; the true charm\nflavour of ghee; delicious taste\nBuddha's gracious teachings" },
	{ "question": "野狐", "answers": [ "やこ" ], "comment": "wild fox\nfox spirit from the Kyushu region capable of possession" },
	{ "question": "銀杏", "answers": [ "ぎんなん" ], "comment": "ginkgo (Ginkgo biloba); gingko; maidenhair tree\nginkgo nut; gingko nut" },
	{ "question": "銅壺", "answers": [ "どうこ" ] },
	{ "question": "錫杖", "answers": [ "しゃくじょう" ], "comment": "bishop's staff; khakkhara" },
	{ "question": "鍍金", "answers": [ "めっき" ], "comment": "plating (chrome, gold, silver, etc.); coating; gilding; gilt\npretense; pretence; simulation" },
	{ "question": "閉塞", "answers": [ "へいそく" ], "comment": "closure; blockage" },
	{ "question": "閏年", "answers": [ "うるうどし", "（じゅんねん）" ], "comment": "leap year" },
	{ "question": "間隙", "answers": [ "かんげき" ], "comment": "gap" },
	{ "question": "雄蕊", "answers": [ "おしべ" ], "comment": "stamen" },
	{ "question": "集輯", "answers": [ "しゅうしゅう" ], "comment": "gathered together and compiled" },
	{ "question": "雌蕊", "answers": [ "めしべ" ], "comment": "pistil" },
	{ "question": "雨蛙", "answers": [ "あまがえる" ], "comment": "tree frog (esp. the Japanese tree frog, Hyla japonica)" },
	{ "question": "雲霞", "answers": [ "うんか" ], "comment": "clouds and haze (fog); disappearing; fleeing" },
	{ "question": "震撼", "answers": [ "しんかん" ], "comment": "shake" },
	{ "question": "霊廟", "answers": [ "れいびょう" ], "comment": "mausoleum" },
	{ "question": "霞む", "answers": [ "かすむ" ], "comment": "to become misty; to become hazy\nto get blurry; to grow dim\nto be overshadowed; to be upstaged; to be outshone" },
	{ "question": "靭帯", "answers": [ "じんたい" ], "comment": "ligament" },
	{ "question": "靱性", "answers": [ "じんせい" ], "comment": "toughness (of a material); tenacity; fracture toughness" },
	{ "question": "鞍上", "answers": [ "あんじょう" ], "comment": "on top of a saddle" },
	{ "question": "鞠問", "answers": [ "きくもん" ], "comment": "examination; interrogation; questioning" },
	{ "question": "頁岩", "answers": [ "けつがん" ], "comment": "shale" },
	{ "question": "領袖", "answers": [ "りょうしゅう" ], "comment": "leader; chief; boss" },
	{ "question": "頸椎", "answers": [ "けいつい" ], "comment": "cervical vertebrae" },
	{ "question": "飴", "answers": [ "あめ" ], "comment": "(hard) candy; toffee\nrice-sugar; sugar made from the starch of rice, potatoes, etc.\namber; yellowish-brown\nconfection (e.g. candy, mochi); sweet" },
	{ "question": "飴煮", "answers": [ "あめに" ], "comment": "food boiled in sugared broth" },
	{ "question": "餌食", "answers": [ "えじき" ], "comment": "prey; victim" },
	{ "question": "饗宴", "answers": [ "きょうえん" ], "comment": "feast; banquet" },
	{ "question": "馨逸", "answers": [ "けいいつ" ] },
	{ "question": "馴化", "answers": [ "じゅんか" ], "comment": "acclimatization; naturalization; acclimation" },
	{ "question": "馴致", "answers": [ "じゅんち" ], "comment": "taming; gradual habituation; leading to" },
	{ "question": "騒擾", "answers": [ "そうじょう" ], "comment": "riot; disturbance" },
	{ "question": "骸骨", "answers": [ "がいこつ" ], "comment": "skeleton" },
	{ "question": "魁偉", "answers": [ "かいい" ], "comment": "brawny; muscular; impressive; gigantic" },
	{ "question": "魁傑", "answers": [ "かいけつ" ] },
	{ "question": "鮎", "answers": [ "あゆ" ], "comment": "sweetfish (Plecoglossus altivelis altivelis); ayu\nsalmon" },
	{ "question": "鯵", "answers": [ "あじ" ], "comment": "horse mackerel (Carangidae spp., esp. the Japanese horse mackerel, Trachurus japonicus); jack mackerel; pompano; scad" },
	{ "question": "鰐", "answers": [ "わに" ], "comment": "crocodile; alligator; crocodilian\nshark" },
	{ "question": "鰭", "answers": [ "ひれ" ], "comment": "fin (e.g. of a fish)" },
	{ "question": "鰹", "answers": [ "かつお" ], "comment": "skipjack tuna (Katsuwonus pelamis); oceanic bonito; victorfish" },
	{ "question": "鳶", "answers": [ "とび", "とんび" ], "comment": "black kite (Milvus migrans)\nconstruction worker; scaffold erector; firefighter\nInverness cape" },
	{ "question": "鴇色", "answers": [ "ときいろ" ], "comment": "pink (wing colour of crested ibis) (color)" },
	{ "question": "鴎", "answers": [ "かもめ" ], "comment": "common gull (Larus canus); mew gull\ngull (Laridae spp.); seagull" },
	{ "question": "鴛鴦", "answers": [ "おしどり" ], "comment": "mandarin duck" },
	{ "question": "鴨", "answers": [ "かも" ], "comment": "duck\neasy mark; sucker; sitting duck" },
	{ "question": "鴨脚", "answers": [ "おうきゃく" ] },
	{ "question": "鶯遷", "answers": [ "おうせん" ], "comment": "warbler flying from a valley to a tree\nfinding success in life\npassing the palace examination" },
	{ "question": "鹿茸", "answers": [ "ろくじょう" ] },
	{ "question": "黍", "answers": [ "きび" ], "comment": "(common) millet (Panicum miliaceium); proso millet" },
	{ "question": "黙祷", "answers": [ "もくとう" ], "comment": "silent prayer" },
	{ "question": "黛青", "answers": [ "たいせい" ], "comment": "blackish blue" },
	{ "question": "鼎談", "answers": [ "ていだん" ], "comment": "tripartite (three man) talk" }
]
}
